

CONTACT

- elena300635@gmail.com
- Białystok, Poland
- in <u>Alena Kavalskaya</u>
- **▼** EIKo3006

HARD SKILLS

- QA testing theory
- Writing test documentation
- Test Case Design
- Understanding clientserver architecture
- API Testing with Postman
- Web testing via DevTools
- Basic knowledge of SQL
- Basic knowledge of HTML, CSS
- Mobile Testing
- Network sniffing with Charles, Fiddler
- Bug tracking via JIRA
- Knowledge of basic Terminal commands
- Version Control with GitHub
- Knowledge of Agile and Scrum development processes

SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Critical Thinking
- Team player
- Communication
- Time Management
- Thirst for learning

Alena Kavalskaya

QA Engineer

PROFILE

I am a a quick learner with a passion for acquiring new knowledge and well-developed logical thinking. My essential qualities are diligence, sociability, responsibility and friendliness. I am excited about the challenges and opportunities that the field of QA engineering presents, and I look forward to contributing my skills and expertise to drive excellence in software quality.

EDUCATION

2012-2018

Bachelor of Medicine

Medical University

WORK EXPERIENCE

june 2023 - Pr.

Trainee QA Engineer

Software mobile app

2019 - 2023

Hygienist of food hygiene department

Center of Hygiene and Epidemiology

Supervisory and oversight activities, making recommendations and setting deadlines for their implementation, education and awareness-raising activities with the population, work with reporting documentation, analysing the results of work

2018 - 2019

Doctor-intern

Center of Hygiene and Epidemiology

Control and supervisory activities, preparation of reports

COURSES

april 2023 - Pr.

Vadim Ksendzov QA Course

august 2023 - Pr.

Ilarion Halushka YouTube course

october 2021 - january 2021

Artsiom Rusau YouTube course